{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326095122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326095122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326100994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326100994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326111112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326111112"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 6f47b094-0854-4b63-b478-3ebcfe7a6fb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_I-U-J"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326117365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326117365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 6f47b094-0854-4b63-b478-3ebcfe7a6fb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_I-A-F"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326123578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326123578"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 6f47b094-0854-4b63-b478-3ebcfe7a6fb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_E-I-T"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326130612","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326130612"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 6f47b094-0854-4b63-b478-3ebcfe7a6fb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_H-P-I"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326134101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326134101"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 6f47b094-0854-4b63-b478-3ebcfe7a6fb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_G-E-I"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326137855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326137854"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 6f47b094-0854-4b63-b478-3ebcfe7a6fb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_A-J-I"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326144831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326144830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 6f47b094-0854-4b63-b478-3ebcfe7a6fb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_F-U-I"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326151661","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326151661"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 6f47b094-0854-4b63-b478-3ebcfe7a6fb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_A-U-I"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326155612","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326155612"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 6f47b094-0854-4b63-b478-3ebcfe7a6fb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_Z-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326160154","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326160154"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 6f47b094-0854-4b63-b478-3ebcfe7a6fb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_V-I-B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326165929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326165929"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 6f47b094-0854-4b63-b478-3ebcfe7a6fb5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_I_V-I-B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326175180","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326175180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_2-11-13"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326180503","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326180503"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_10-5-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326186185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326186185"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326193090","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326193090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326199302","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326199302"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326206596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326206596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-0-11"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326213030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326213030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-0-11"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326218711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326218711"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-11-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326224721","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326224721"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-10-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326233310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326233310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-1-10"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326243811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326243811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-1-2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326253327","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326253327"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-10-12"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326285886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326285885"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-10-12"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326294790","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326294790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-10-12"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326299975","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326299975"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_0-10-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326368685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326368684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_0-10-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326375219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326375218"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_10_0-10-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326395267","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326395266"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_10_0-10-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326402913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326402913"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" de62d051-af50-4c22-bca5-12dedf4f0b6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_10_0-10-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326419247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326419247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326420308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326420307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326423786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326423786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326424848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326424847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326434901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326434901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326435962","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326435962"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326438914","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326438913"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326439116","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326439116"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326440023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326440023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326441340","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326441340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326442458","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326442458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326443750","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326443750"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326444869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326444868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326446042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326446042"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326447137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326447137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326449989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326449989"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326454890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326454890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326455923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326455923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326459288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326459288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326460322","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326460322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326463156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326463156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326464205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326464205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326470013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326470012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326471080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326471080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326475615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326475614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326476656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326476656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326483689","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326483689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326484751","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326484751"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326488616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326488616"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326489660","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326489660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326493725","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326493725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326494755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326494755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326497644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326497643"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326498163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326498163"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326499292","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326499292"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326499622","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326499622"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326508228","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326508228"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326515681","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326515681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 88b6b83c-482a-465f-bc94-c7885683c12a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326564224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326564224"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" cd7e10c0-4bfe-4127-8c06-49ddb2f2ab0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326586473","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326586473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" cd7e10c0-4bfe-4127-8c06-49ddb2f2ab0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326636303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326636302"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" cd7e10c0-4bfe-4127-8c06-49ddb2f2ab0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326639553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326639553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" cd7e10c0-4bfe-4127-8c06-49ddb2f2ab0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326673438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326673437"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" cd7e10c0-4bfe-4127-8c06-49ddb2f2ab0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326673537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326673537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" cd7e10c0-4bfe-4127-8c06-49ddb2f2ab0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326680483","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326680482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" cd7e10c0-4bfe-4127-8c06-49ddb2f2ab0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..22.off2.17__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326715110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326715109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" cd7e10c0-4bfe-4127-8c06-49ddb2f2ab0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326735431","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326735431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326740624","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326740624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326762264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326762264"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326766474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326766474"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326776479","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326776479"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326780364","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326780364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326787815","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326787815"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326791553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326791553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326794683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326794683"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326798618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326798618"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326812612","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326812612"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326826323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326826323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326833792","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326833792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326839785","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326839785"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326861076","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326861076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326866830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326866830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326870543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326870543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326876906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326876905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326881501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326881501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326891973","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326891973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326896157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326896157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326899159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326899158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326902056","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326902056"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326905058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326905058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326908488","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326908488"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326914231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326914229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 775f6678-21b2-4fcb-9650-aa3bf9c0749a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326957740","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326957740"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be592584-b48f-4802-94fd-c338420a42f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326994045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326994045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be592584-b48f-4802-94fd-c338420a42f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548326998076","data":{"timestamp":" 1548326998076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be592584-b48f-4802-94fd-c338420a42f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327043330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327043330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be592584-b48f-4802-94fd-c338420a42f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327043405","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327043405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be592584-b48f-4802-94fd-c338420a42f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327088210","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327088209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" c42545e9-154a-4c88-99c8-dde8d0c36f47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327136783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327136783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" c42545e9-154a-4c88-99c8-dde8d0c36f47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327136855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327136855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" c42545e9-154a-4c88-99c8-dde8d0c36f47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327144310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327144310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 65ab7cfc-4886-4b45-a9fb-aca7f4ebe388"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_N-J-Z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327147251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327147251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 65ab7cfc-4886-4b45-a9fb-aca7f4ebe388"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-U-K"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327150288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327150288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 65ab7cfc-4886-4b45-a9fb-aca7f4ebe388"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_K-J-T"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327153509","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327153509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 65ab7cfc-4886-4b45-a9fb-aca7f4ebe388"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_R-D-J"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327156466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327156466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 65ab7cfc-4886-4b45-a9fb-aca7f4ebe388"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_E-J-O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327159751","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327159751"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 65ab7cfc-4886-4b45-a9fb-aca7f4ebe388"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-J-N"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327163343","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327163343"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 65ab7cfc-4886-4b45-a9fb-aca7f4ebe388"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_D-V-J"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327166686","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327166686"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 65ab7cfc-4886-4b45-a9fb-aca7f4ebe388"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_S-E-J"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327169866","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327169866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 65ab7cfc-4886-4b45-a9fb-aca7f4ebe388"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_L-J-G"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327174462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327174462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 65ab7cfc-4886-4b45-a9fb-aca7f4ebe388"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-D-E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327180205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327180205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 65ab7cfc-4886-4b45-a9fb-aca7f4ebe388"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-D-E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327191044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327191044"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_1-10-11"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327196026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327196026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_8-2-11"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327206211","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327206211"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_8-2-11"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327213086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327213086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_8-2-11"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327222606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327222605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_13_10-12-13"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 13"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327229147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327229146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_13_10-12-13"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 13"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327235722","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327235722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_13_10-12-13"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 13"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327242294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327242294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_3-13-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327248440","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327248440"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-11-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327253492","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327253492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327259126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327259126"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_8-1-11"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327268069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327268069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_8-1-11"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327289372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327289372"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-2-7"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327295733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327295733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-2-7"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327301856","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327301856"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-11-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327317660","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327317660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-11-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327342087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327342087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-0-10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327348731","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327348730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" d8a79d70-4bbc-409d-a916-de48ca9c8be7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-0-10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327369352","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327369351"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" ca55f763-edd8-4844-8bdb-7dd525035aff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-B-J"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327372767","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327372767"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" ca55f763-edd8-4844-8bdb-7dd525035aff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-W-P"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327405893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327405892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" ca55f763-edd8-4844-8bdb-7dd525035aff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_R-J-N"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327409367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327409367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" ca55f763-edd8-4844-8bdb-7dd525035aff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_U-J-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327425119","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327425119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" ca55f763-edd8-4844-8bdb-7dd525035aff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_A-E-J"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327435237","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327435237"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" ca55f763-edd8-4844-8bdb-7dd525035aff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_M-N-J"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327444681","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327444681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" ca55f763-edd8-4844-8bdb-7dd525035aff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_M-N-J"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327459071","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327459070"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" ca55f763-edd8-4844-8bdb-7dd525035aff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_D-J-Y"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327487412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327487412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" ca55f763-edd8-4844-8bdb-7dd525035aff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_K-O-J"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327502771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327502771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" ca55f763-edd8-4844-8bdb-7dd525035aff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_P-E-J"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327505843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327505842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" ca55f763-edd8-4844-8bdb-7dd525035aff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-E-Y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327511613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327511610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" ca55f763-edd8-4844-8bdb-7dd525035aff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-E-Y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327525541","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327525541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be9ab648-1bae-4383-b0ca-50ac74eeb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-B-J"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327550609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327550609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be9ab648-1bae-4383-b0ca-50ac74eeb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-E-Y"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327554768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327554767"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be9ab648-1bae-4383-b0ca-50ac74eeb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_R-J-N"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327558686","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327558686"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be9ab648-1bae-4383-b0ca-50ac74eeb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-W-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327562776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327562776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be9ab648-1bae-4383-b0ca-50ac74eeb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_P-E-J"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327575215","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327575215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be9ab648-1bae-4383-b0ca-50ac74eeb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_A-E-J"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327585503","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327585503"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be9ab648-1bae-4383-b0ca-50ac74eeb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_M-N-J"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327596727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327596727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be9ab648-1bae-4383-b0ca-50ac74eeb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_U-J-D"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327620208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327620208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be9ab648-1bae-4383-b0ca-50ac74eeb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_K-O-J"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327625532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327625532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be9ab648-1bae-4383-b0ca-50ac74eeb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_D-J-Y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327631282","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327631279"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be9ab648-1bae-4383-b0ca-50ac74eeb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_J_D-J-Y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327647978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327647978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be9ab648-1bae-4383-b0ca-50ac74eeb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_D-J-Y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327655793","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327655792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be9ab648-1bae-4383-b0ca-50ac74eeb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_D-J-Y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327663426","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327663426"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be9ab648-1bae-4383-b0ca-50ac74eeb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_D-J-Y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327671471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327671471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be9ab648-1bae-4383-b0ca-50ac74eeb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_D-J-Y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327677958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327677958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" be9ab648-1bae-4383-b0ca-50ac74eeb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_D-J-Y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327689145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327689145"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" aadf21a2-e9d6-4570-ab2b-a7f1d4d086b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-B-J"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327690419","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327690419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" aadf21a2-e9d6-4570-ab2b-a7f1d4d086b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-B-J"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327698566","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327698566"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" aadf21a2-e9d6-4570-ab2b-a7f1d4d086b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-B-J"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327705935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327705935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" aadf21a2-e9d6-4570-ab2b-a7f1d4d086b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-B-J"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327712680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327712679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" aadf21a2-e9d6-4570-ab2b-a7f1d4d086b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-B-J"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327720192","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327720192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" aadf21a2-e9d6-4570-ab2b-a7f1d4d086b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-B-J"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327727038","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327727037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" aadf21a2-e9d6-4570-ab2b-a7f1d4d086b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-B-J"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327733635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327733635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" aadf21a2-e9d6-4570-ab2b-a7f1d4d086b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-B-J"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327740584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327740583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" aadf21a2-e9d6-4570-ab2b-a7f1d4d086b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-B-J"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327747798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327747797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" aadf21a2-e9d6-4570-ab2b-a7f1d4d086b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-B-J"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327754866","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327754866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" aadf21a2-e9d6-4570-ab2b-a7f1d4d086b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-B-J"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327762115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327762115"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" aadf21a2-e9d6-4570-ab2b-a7f1d4d086b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-B-J"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327781714","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327781714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 099d54f0-2bc1-4190-a3be-3f81c960c407"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-W-P"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327787478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327787478"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 099d54f0-2bc1-4190-a3be-3f81c960c407"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_D-J-Y"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327791871","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327791871"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 099d54f0-2bc1-4190-a3be-3f81c960c407"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_CH-B-J"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327795607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327795607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 099d54f0-2bc1-4190-a3be-3f81c960c407"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_M-N-J"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548327797459","data":{"timestamp":" 1548327797459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_133440"," gameId":" 099d54f0-2bc1-4190-a3be-3f81c960c407"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_J_M-N-J"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}